

## Frédéric Vandeborne

Passionate Front-End & Drupal developer, with a strong knowledge of webdevelopment. Eager to experiment with new stacks.

- in linkedin.com/in/fredericvandeborne
- github.com/chezfre
- www.chezfre.be
- 🍮 12 juni 1989

I'm an Acquia Certified Drupal Front-End Developer and Sitebuilder, and most of the client work I have done for the past 5 years has revolved around Drupal. My personal area of interest is JavaScript, and in my free time I frequently dabble with vanilla Javascript, the Node runtime, Angular and React.

Webdevelopment is not just a job, it's a passion that I'm constantly working on improving and expanding by reading and experimenting.

## Projects (LinkedIn for more)

## Impact Interim

Drupal 7 · Responsive · Multilingual · User login www.impact.be

## Lamb Weston - Twist your fries

Responsive · Parallax www.chezfre.be/LambWeston

### Van Eycken

Drupal 7 · Responsive · Multilingual www.vaneycken.be

### Hegro België

Drupal 7 · Responsive · Multilingual http://hegro.dev1.novation.be

### Sentilo

Drupal 7 · Design www.sentilo.be

## Leffe Hop Harvest Day

Angular 1.5

http://vd4906.dev1.novation.be

# **Professional experience**

### Novation

www.novation.be

After my internship, I was offered a job at this startup webdevelopment agency. Since february 2012, I've helped grow Novation to a flourishing Drupal shop. As more people joined the team, I've taken up the task of team lead. In this position I have worked on streamlining our development process by automating our Drupal setup and Front-end compilation/optimization.

FEBRUARY - JUNE 2012 Internship

JUNE 2012 - NOW Drupal & Front-End Developer

JANUARY 2016 - NOW + Team Lead

### Zorro

www.zorro.be

In a partnership between Novation and Don Diego I've freelanced over a three year period, both remote and on-site for various clients including Telenet, Deloitte, Unilever and Renault.

MAY 2012 - DECEMBER 2015 Freelance developer

# **Education**

## High School

Economie Moderne Talen Heilig Graf Bilzen 2001 - 2007

### Acquia Ce

Certificates

Acquia Certified Drupal Site Builder 2016 Acquia Certified Front-End Specialist 2016 AnySurfer - accessibility course 2017







## **Higher Education**

New Media And Communication Technology Hogeschool West-Vlaanderen 2007 - 2008

Devine - Digital Design And Media Hogeschool West-Vlaanderen 2008 - 2012